Guide to the George Adams Shuford Papers, 1952-1959
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Correspondence Series
  - Young, Mr. Quatermaster Market Center (Box 21)
  - Young, Sue (Box 21)
  - Y (Box 21)
  - XYZ (Box 21)
- Letters: Legislation
  - Letters. 1953, Jan.-March (Box 22)
  - Letters. 1953, April-June (Box 22)
  - Letters. 1953, July-September (Box 23)
  - Letters. 1953, October-December (Box 23)
  - Letters. 1954, January-March (Box 23)
  - Letters. 1954, April-June (Box 23)
  - Letters. 1954, July-September (Box 23)
  - Letters. 1954, August-December (Box 23)
  - Letters. 1955, April-December (Box 23)
  - Letters.1956 (Box 23)
  - Letters.1957 (Box 23)
  - Letters.1958 (Box 23)
- Letters: General
  - Letters. 1953, January-March (Box 24)
  - Letters. 1953, April-June (Box 25)
  - Letters. 1953, July-September (Box 25)
  - Letters. 1953, October-December (Box 25)
  - Letters. 1954, January-March (Box 26)
  - Letters. 1954, April-June (Box 26)
  - Letters. 1954, July-September (Box 26)
  - Letters. 1954, October-December (Box 26)
  - Letters. 1955, January-March (Box 26)
  - Letters.1956 (Box 27)
  - Letters.1957 (Box 27)
  - Letters.1958 (Box 28)
- Letters: Congratulations, Recommendations, References, and Sympathy
  - Congratulatory and Recommendations. Also Sympathy. 1953-1954 (Box 28)
  - Congratulatory Letters.1954 (Box 28)
  - Congratulations and Sympathy. 1957-1958 (Box 28)
  - References and Recommendations.1953 - 1958 (Box 28)
- Volumes
  - Guest Book. 1953-1956 (Box 28)
  - Guest Book. 1956-1958 (Box 28)
- Inaugural Invitation
  - Inaugural Invitation.1953 (Box 28)
- Speeches
  - Speech delivered at St. Francis High School. June 4,1953 (Box 29)
  - Speech given before the Osteo-Pathic Society Re: OA (Box 29)
  - Speech given at Lions Club. Sept. 24,1952 (Box 29)
  - Notes on Cherokee delivered at Lions Club. 1956 (Box 29)
  - Black,Eugene R. (Box 29)
  - Speech over Station WLOS/League of Women Voters. May 16, 1958 (Box 29)
  - Speech by Judge Shuford before the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers. Asheville. May 26, 1955 (Box 29)
  - Speech to be made at Cullowhee. Research and the Graduate (Box 29)
  - Veterans Speech Notes (Box 29)
  - This is the Law. T.V. Program (Box 29)
  - Speech of Hon. Jas. O. Eastland. May 26, 1955. The Supreme Courts 'Modern Scientific Authorities' in the Segregation Cases (Box 29)
  - Speech given before Optimist Club. Oct. 14, 1957 (Box 29)
  - Speech. N.C. Food Dealers Asso. (Box 29)
  - Mr. Shuford's Talks (Box 29)
  - Asheville Chamber of Commerce. Introduction. Sen. McClellan. Jan., 1958 (Box 29)
  - Speech before V.F.W. Asheville. Feb. 1, 1958 (Box 29)
  - Speech presented at Buncombe Democratic Convention. May 15, 1954 (Box 29)
  - Rural Electrification Speech Notes (Box 29)
  - Speech. REA (Box 29)
  - Speech Material (Box 30)
- Subject Files Series
  - Addresses (Box 31)
  - Agencies. Information (Box 31)
  - Agriculture:
    - Asiatic Beetle. Haywood County (Box 31)
    - Bulletins, 1953-1954 (Box 31)
    - Bulletins, 1954 (Box 31)
    - Bulletins, 1955-1956 (Box 31)
    - Bulletins, 1957-1958 (Box 31)
    - Buncombe County ASC Office Investigation (Box 32)
    - Cane Creek. Buncombe County. Soil Conservation Service (Box 32)
    - Copies of Bills. 1955-1956 (Box 32)
    - Copies of Bills. 1957-1958 (Box 32)
    - Department of Agriculture. 1953 (Box 32)
    - Department of Agriculture. 1954-1958 (Box 32)
    - Department of Agriculture. Reorganization (Box 32)
    - Department of Agriculture. Soil Conservation (Box 32)
    - Extension of Remarks. James G. K. McClure. (Box 32)
    - Farmers Federation (Box 32)
    - Farm Program (Box 32)
    - Farmers Federation Cooperative (Box 32)
    - Farmers Union Program (Box 33)
    - Flexible Farm Program (Box 33)
    - General (Box 33)
    - Haywood County Farm Group (Box 33)
    - Hendersonville Gladiolus Growers Assoc. (Box 33)
    - Legislation. 1955-1956 (Box 33)
    - Legislation. 1957-1958 (Box 33)
  - Agriculture (Box 34)
    - Agricultural Conservation Program. HR 4877. 1953-1958 (Box 34)
    - N.C. Agricultural Statistics.1954 (Box 34)
    - North Carolina Farm Bureau Federation Inc. 1955 (Box 34)
    - Parity Price Support Program (Box 34)
    - Reports. Annual. North Carolina. 1953 (Box 34)
    - Soil Survey of Buncombe County. 1954 (Box 34)
    - Soil Survey. Cherokee and Jackson. 1957 (Box 34)
    - Soil Survey. Haywood County. 1956 (Box 34)
    - Soil Survey. Macon County. 1956 (Box 34)
    - Soybean Standards (Box 34)
    - Veto of Farm Bill. Senate discussion. 4/16/56 (Box 34)
    - Watershed Protection Act. (Soil Conservation Service). 1954 (Box 34)
  - Agriculture Yearbooks:
    - Yearbooks. 1950-1951 (Box 34)
    - Yearbooks.1952 (Box 34)
    - Yearbooks.1953 (Box 35)
    - Yearbooks.1954 (Box 35)
    - Yearbooks.1955 (Box 35)
    - Yearbooks.1956 (Box 35)
    - Yearbooks.1957 (Box 35)
    - Yearbooks. Misc. (Box 35)
    - Yearbooks. Various Years (Box 35)
  - Air Lines (Box 36)
  - American Legion:
    - Convention. 1954 (Box 36)
    - General. 1957-1958 (Box 36)
  - Applications:
    - Applications (Box 36)
    - For Jobs in New Congress.1954 (Box 36)
    - Job Applications.1953 (Box 36)
  - Appropriations:
    - Copies of Bills. 1955-1956 (Box 36)
    - Copies of Bills. 1957-1958 (Box 36)
    - Legislation. Various Years (Box 36)
    - Legislation. 1957-1958 (Box 36)
    - Supplemental Approp. Implement. P.L. 733 (Box 37)
  - Arlington Memorial Amphitheater. Prohibiting the erection of carillons on the land of the U.S. near. H.R. 13785. 1958 (Box 37)
  - Armed Services:
    - Copies of Bills.1955 (Box 37)
    - Copies of Bills. 1957-1958 (Box 37)
    - Department of Air Force. 1955. 1957-1958 (Box 37)
    - Department of Army. 1955. 1957-1958 (Box 37)
    - Legislation. 1955-1956 (Box 37)
    - Legislation. 1957-1958 (Box 37)
    - Reserve Bill.1955 (Box 37)
    - Universal Military Training (Box 37)
  - Asheville: (Box 38)
    - Airport (Box 38)
    - Airport (Box 38)
    - Airport (Box 38)
    - Arcade Building (Box 38)
    - Bill for Relief of Dixie Novelty Co. 1955.H.R. 2784 (Box 38)
    - Country Day School (Box 38)
    - Federal Agency Transfer (Box 38)
    - Industrial Council. 1953-1954 (Box 38)
    - Industrial Council.1955 (Box 38)
    - Industrial Council. 1957-1958 (Box 38)
    - Mills Manufacturing Corporation (Box 38)
    - Wise (Box 38)
    - Wise. T.V. (Box 39)
  - Atomic Energy:
    - Atomic Energy Commission. 1955. 1957-1958 (Box 39)
    - H.R. 9757. S. 3690. Amend Atomic Energy Com. Act. 1954 (Box 39)
    - Joint Committee on Atomic Energy (Box 39)
    - Joint Committee on Atomic Energy. Legislation. 1957-1958 (Box 39)
  - Blue Ridge Parkway:
    - Blue Ridge Parkway Office (Box 39)
    - Blue Ridge. 1954 (Box 39)
    - Blue Ridge Parkway. 1955-1956 (Box 39)
    - Blue Ridge Parkway. 1957-1958 (Box 39)
    - Blue Ridge Parkway. misc. (Box 40)
    - Blue Ridge Parkway. misc. (Box 40)
    - H.R. 11055. To Provide that the Blue Ridge Parkway shall be toll free. 1955-1958 (Box 40)
    - H.R. 10540. To Provide that the Blue Ridge Parkway shall be toll free.1956 (Box 40)
    - Spalling (Box 40)
  - Chief Blythe (Box 40)
  - Brittain Hosiery Mills (Box 40)
  - Brumbaugh. H.R. 7713. Relief of Hertha Stammler Brumbaugh (Box 41)
  - Bryson City:
    - Federal Building. H.R. 9137 (Box 41)
    - H.R. 8988. To Provide for the construction of a new post office, fed. courthouse, and fed. office building (Box 41)
  - Burley Tobacco. H.R. 9148 (Box 41)
  - Calendars.1957 (Box 41)
  - Campaign:
    - Campaign for the 48 States (Box 41)
    - Congressional.1954 (Box 41)
    - Material (Box 41)
    - Stevenson Campaign.1956 (Box 41)
  - The Capitol (Box 41)
  - Cemeteries visited while on trip (Box 41)
  - Cherokee:
    - Cherokee. 1955 (Box 41)
    - Cherokee Development Program (Box 41)
    - Cherokee. General.1956 (Box 41)
    - Cherokee. General.1957 (Box 41)
    - Cherokee Hearings. September,1955 (Box 41)
    - Cherokee Indian Res. Food Contract.1955 (Box 42)
    - Proposed School Buildings (Box 42)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board. 1955 (Box 42)
  - Civil Rights:
    - Civil Rights. General (Box 42)
    - H.R. 2145. To Provide means at further securing and protecting the civil rights of persons within the jurisdiction of the U.S.1957 (Box 42)
    - H.R. 6127.1957 (Box 42)
    - Integration. General (Box 42)
    - Segregation (Box 42)
    - Segregation at Oteen (Box 42)
    - Segregation Resolution of March 12, 1956 (Box 42)
  - Civil Service Commission. 1955 (Box 42)
  - Civil Service: (Box 43)
    - Retirement System (Box 43)
    - To Increase annuities payable to certain annuitants from the civil service retirement and disability fund, etc. H.R. 4427.1957 (Box 43)
  - Clerks:
    - Applications. Clerical (Box 43)
    - Clerk Hire (Box 43)
    - Clerk's Office. Correspondence (Box 43)
  - Cocke, Philip C. 1957 (Box 43)
  - Colorado River:
    - Colorado River (Box 43)
    - Colorado River Project (Box 43)
    - Colorado Storage Project (Box 43)
    - Daily Folder. Current Correspondence (Box 43)
    - Irrigation Subcommittee. Upper Colorado legislation. 1955-1956 (Box 43)
    - Irrigation Subcommittee. Upper Colorado legislation. 1955-1956 (Box 44)
    - Reports on H.R. 3383. Upper Colorado (Box 44)
  - Commerce:
    - Copies of Bills. Interstate and Foreign Commerce. 1955-1957 (Box 44)
    - Department of Commerce. 1955. 1957-1958 (Box 44)
    - GATT. General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (Box 44)
    - H.R.-1. Rec. Trade. 1956 (Box 45)
    - H.R. 7417. Repeal Case in Tariff Ways and Means. 1956 (Box 45)
    - H.R. 4294. Reciprocal Trade Act (Box 45)
    - House Document 99. Federal Medical Services. CIFC. 1955 (Box 45)
    - Legislation. Interstate and Foreign Commerce. 1955-1956 (Box 45)
    - Legislation. Interstate and Foreign Commerce. 1957-1958 (Box 45)
  - Communism (Box 46)
  - Congress:
    - Correspondence. Members of Congress. 1955-1956 (Box 46)
    - Correspondence. Members of Congress. 1957 (Box 46)
    - Congressional Poll. 1953 (Box 46)
    - Congressional Directory. 1955-1956 (Box 46)
    - Congressional Directory. 1957-1958 (Box 46)
    - Congressional Record. Remarks. 1956 (Box 46)
    - Congressional Record. Remarks. 1957-1958 (Box 46)
    - Congressional Record. 1957-1958 (Box 46)
  - Constitution:
    - Bricker Amendment (Box 46)
    - H.J. Res. 448. Proposing an Amendment to the Constitution with respect to the admission of new states as sovereign states of the United States. 1957 (Box 46)
    - Info. on Constitution (Box 46)
    - Declaration of Constitutional Principles Department of Defense. 1955. 1957-1958 (Box 46)
    - Young Democratic Club Letter. Re: Tom Garrison Letter.1953 (Box 46)
  - Democratic: (Box 47)
    - Democratic Rally. Oct. 5, 1954 (Box 47)
    - Democratic Rallies. 12th District (Box 47)
  - Democratic Party:
    - Jefferson-Jackson Dinner. 1954 (Box 47)
    - Jefferson-Jackson Dinner. 1955 (Box 47)
  - Democratic National Committee:
    - 1955-1956 (Box 47)
    - 1956 (Box 47)
    - Newspaper Info. News Releases (Box 47)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 47)
  - Disaster:
    - Banking and Currency. Hurricane and Disaster Legislation. 1955-1956 (Box 47)
    - Drought and Disaster Program (Box 47)
    - Disaster Loans (Box 47)
  - District of Columbia:
    - Copies of Bills. 1957-1958 (Box 47)
    - Legislation. 1955-1956 (Box 47)
  - District Office: (Box 48)
    - District Office (Box 48)
    - Expenses (Box 48)
  - Echo Park (Box 48)
  - Echo Park Dam (Box 48)
  - Education:
    - Copies of Bills. Education and Labor. 1955 (Box 48)
    - Federal Aid to Education. H.R. 7535 (Box 48)
    - Legislation. Education and Labor. 1955 (Box 48)
    - Legislation. Education and Labor. 1957-1958 (Box 49)
    - Oil for Education Bill. S. 772. Sen. Hill, Scott, etc. (Box 49)
    - S.S. Sen. Hill. 30 other senators (Box 49)
    - School Groups.1954. 1957-1958 (Box 49)
    - School Groups.1955. 1956 (Box 49)
    - School Lunch Program (Box 49)
    - Vocational Educational Funds (Box 49)
  - Electrical:
    - Equipment (Box 49)
    - Electric Power (Box 49)
    - Private Power Companies. rapid amortization cert. (Box 49)
    - Public and Private Power (Box 49)
    - Tarheel Electric Membership Ass'n. Inc. (Box 49)
    - Rural Elcetric Association (Box 49)
    - Rural Electrification (Box 50)
  - Employment Service. United States (Box 50)
  - Extension of Remarks (Box 50)
  - Falson Dam Bill. H.R. 8328 (Box 50)
  - Federal Housing Administration (Box 50)
  - Federal Power Commission. 1955 (Box 50)
  - Federal Register (Box 50)
  - FHA Appraiser (Box 50)
  - Finance:
    - Banking and Currency. 1955-1956 (Box 50)
    - Copies of Bills. Banking and Currency. 1955-1956 (Box 50)
    - Copies of Bills. Banking and Currency. 1957-1958 (Box 50)
    - Legislation. Banking and Currency. 1957-1958 (Box 50)
    - Legislation. Senate Finance Committee. 1957-1958 (Box 50)
  - Fish (Box 50)
  - Fish and Wildlife (Box 51)
  - Fluoridation Program. H.R. 2341 (Box 51)
  - Fontana Drug Store. Inc. (Box 51)
  - Fontana Village (Box 51)
  - Football Tickets:
    - Applications for1957football tickets (Navy Academy, West Point) (Box 51)
    - Football Tickets (Box 51)
  - Foreign Affairs:
    - Copies of Bills. 1955-1956 (Box 51)
    - Copies of Bills. 1957-1958 (Box 51)
    - Legislation. 1955-1956 (Box 51)
    - Legislation. 1957-1958 (Box 52)
  - Foreign Service (Box 52)
  - Forest Service. Dept. of Agriculture. 1957-1958 (Box 52)
  - French Broad River:
    - Flood Prevention Problem (Box 52)
    - Highway (Box 52)
    - 1 tr. from Mrs. Riley (Box 52)
  - Frying Pan (Box 52)
  - Frying Pan. Arkansas Project (Box 52)
  - General Services Administration. 1955 (Box 52)
  - Government Operations:
    - Copies of Bills. 1957-1958 (Box 52)
    - Kennedy-Rogers Bill. 1957 (Box 52)
    - Legislation. 1955-1956 (Box 52)
    - Legislation. 1957-1958 (Box 52)
  - Government Printing Office (Box 53)
  - Great Smoky Mountains National Park (Box 53)
  - Haberis. H.R.1988.Relief of Gerasimos Athanase Haberis (Box 53)
  - Haley-Shuford minority Report. Final Draft. H.R. 3384 (Box 53)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare. 1955. 1957-1958 (Box 53)
  - Heintooga. Editorials on (Box 53)
  - Hell's Canyon Dam (Box 53)
  - Hell's Canyon Dam Legislation and Committee (Box 53)
  - Hell's Canyon Legislation.1958 (Box 53)
  - Highway: (Box 54)
    - Highway Districts (Box 54)
    - Highway Legislation. 1456 (Box 54)
    - Highway Revenue. H.R. 9075 (Box 54)
    - Proposed highway Program. H.R. 7072 (Box 54)
  - Hoey, Clyde R. Statement to the Press (Box 54)
  - Hoover Comm. Report (Box 54)
  - Hopper, Relief of George D. H.R.1989 (Box 54)
  - House of Representatives
    - Copies of Bills. House Administration. 1955 (Box 54)
    - Legislation. House Administration. 1956-1958 (Box 54)
    - Legislation. Rules. 1955-1956 (Box 54)
  - Housing Bill. H R 7839 (Box 54)
  - Housing and Home Finance Agency. 1955 (Box 55)
  - Immigration:
    - H.R.1990.Relief of Michael Aristides Tsperkas (Box 55)
    - H.R. 5678. Immigration and Nationality Act (Box 55)
    - McCarran Act (Box 55)
  - Inauguration. 1953 (Box 55)
  - Inauguration.1957 (Box 55)
  - Indian Affairs (Box 55)
  - Indian Affairs (Box 55)
  - Indian Affairs: (Box 56)
    - Cherokee Indians (Box 56)
    - General (Box 56)
    - General Correspondence (Box 56)
    - General Legislation. 1955-1956 (Box 56)
    - H.R. 4830. To Authorize revision of the Tribal roll of the Eastern Band of Cherokee Indians, N.C. and for other purposes (Box 56)
    - Legislation.1957 (Box 56)
    - Legislation. Committee.1954 (Box 56)
    - Osage (Box 57)
    - Seminole Indian Florida Trip (Box 57)
    - Sioux Indians (Box 57)
    - Subcommittee. General .1957 (Box 57)
    - Subcommittee. Termination Legislation. 1955 (Box 57)
    - Ute (Box 57)
  - Industries. New in Western N.C. (Box 57)
  - Information Service. U.S. 1955 (Box 57)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs. H.R. 89. 1953 (Box 57)
  - Department of Interior. 1955. 1957-1958.2-3982 (Box 57)
  - H. Con. Res. 106. Int. and Insular Affairs (Box 57)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs: (Box 58)
    - Committee. General.1957 (Box 58)
    - Committee. Misc. (Box 58)
    - Committee. Misc. (Box 58)
    - Committee. Misc. (Box 59)
    - Committee. Misc. (Box 59)
    - General Correspondence. 1955-1956 (Box 59)
  - Invitations: (Box 60)
    - Invitations. 1953 (Box 60)
    - Invitations.1954 (Box 60)
    - Invitations.1954 (Box 60)
    - Invitations. Pending.1955 (Box 60)
    - Invitations.1955 (Box 60)
    - Invitations.1956 (Box 61)
    - Invitations.1956 (Box 61)
    - Invitations.1957 (Box 61)
    - Invitations.1957 (Box 61)
    - Invitations.1958 (Box 62)
    - Invitations.1958 (Box 62)
  - Irrigation and Reclamation Subcommittee:
    - General.1957 (Box 62)
    - General Correspondence (Box 62)
    - General Legislation. 1955-1956 (Box 62)
    - Legislation.1957 (Box 62)
  - Judiciary Committee: (Box 63)
    - Additional Judgeship for State of North Carolina. H.R. 3559 (Box 63)
    - Adjust Salaries of Judges. Members of Congress, etc. H.R. 3828 (Box 63)
    - Bryson City, N. C. (Box 63)
    - Copies of Bills.1945. 1955 (Box 63)
    - Copies of Bills. 1957-1958 (Box 63)
    - H.R. 5824 (Box 63)
    - Legislation. 1955-1956 (Box 63)
    - Legislation. 1957-1958 (Box 63)
    - Pay Raise for Congressmen and Judges (Box 63)
  - Department of Justice. 1955 (Box 64)
  - Kerr. H.R. 10245. For the Relief of Cecil Laing Kerr (Box 64)
  - Department of Labor:
    - Department of Labor. 1955 (Box 64)
    - Taft-Hartley (Box 64)
    - Taft-Hartley Act (Box 64)
    - Union Shops (Box 64)
    - Vocational Rehabilitation and Education (Box 64)
  - League of Women Voters (Box 64)
  - League of Women Voters (Box 64)
  - Library of Congress (Box 64)
  - Liquor Advertising. H.R. 1227. Bryson Bill (Box 64)
  - Maps (New) United States (Box 64)
  - McCarthy Controversy (Box 64)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries:
    - Legislation. H.R. 19 (Box 64)
    - Legislation. 1955-1956 (Box 64)
    - Legislation. 1957-1958 (Box 64)
    - National Committee (Box 64)
  - Minerals (Box 64)
  - Mines and Mining (Box 64)
  - Mines and Mining Subcommittee: (Box 65)
    - Feldspar (Box 65)
    - General.1957 (Box 65)
    - General Correspondence. (Box 65)
    - General Legislation. 1955-1956 (Box 65)
    - Legislation.1957 (Box 65)
    - MICA. 1953-1954 (Box 65)
    - MICA. Import Study (Box 65)
    - To Provide for the maintenance of essential production of tungsten ores and concentrate in the U.S. H.R. 9820 (Box 65)
  - Mission-66. 1956 (Box 65)
  - Morgan. H.R. 6824. A Bill for the Relief of the Family of Joseph A. Morgan (Box 65)
  - Mud Creek Watershed Project (Box 65)
  - Mutual Security Act (Box 65)
  - National Forests: (Box 66)
    - Forest Service. Department of Agriculture (Box 66)
    - H.R.1972. National Forests (Box 66)
    - H.R. 9822. To provide for the establishment of a trout hatchery on the Davidson River in the Pisgah National Forest in N.C. (Box 66)
    - Mt. Pisgah Television Tower (Box 66)
    - Nantahala National Forest (Box 66)
    - National Forests (Box 66)
  - National Gallery of Art (Box 66)
  - National Park Service:
    - Appropriation for National Park Service. H.R. 4828 (Box 66)
    - Bear Problem. Smoky Mt. Area (Box 66)
    - Editorials (Box 66)
    - General (Box 66)
    - Travel Survey. Yosemite (Box 66)
  - Department of Navy. 1955 (Box 67)
  - Newsletter (Box 67)
  - Newspapers and Clippings (Box 67)
  - North Carolina:
    - Federal Offices closed in N.C. (Box 67)
    - General. 1955-1956 (Box 67)
    - General.1957 (Box 67)
  - North Carolina. 12th District: (Box 68)
    - Buncombe. Political (Box 68)
    - Cherokee. Political (Box 68)
    - Clay. Political (Box 68)
    - Graham. Political (Box 68)
    - Haywood. Political (Box 68)
    - Henderson. Political (Box 68)
    - Info. Re: 12th District (Box 68)
    - Jackson. Political (Box 68)
    - Macon. Political (Box 68)
    - North Carolina. 12th District (Box 68)
    - Swain. Political (Box 68)
    - Translyvania. Political (Box 68)
  - Oerlikon (Box 68)
  - Oteen (Box 68)
  - Oteen Advisor Matter (Box 68)
  - Oteen V.A. Hospitals (Box 68)
  - Pages (Box 68)
  - Pakistan. Wheat for Pakistan. H.R. 5659. Congressional Record. June 23, 1953 (Box 68)
  - Passports (Box 68)
  - Pattison. Hortense R. (Harold Shuttles). H.R. 9116 (Box 69)
  - Personnel (Box 69)
  - Photographers (Box 69)
  - Pigeon River Project (Box 69)
  - Pledge of Allegiance to Flag. State Joint Resolution 126. Under God (Box 69)
  - Political. General (Box 69)
  - Post Office:
    - Clerks (Box 69)
    - Legislation. H.R. 1826. Postal. Moss. Of Calif. (Box 69)
    - Legislation. H.R. 2297. P.O. Employees Salary. H.R. 2344. Salary Adjustment (Box 69)
    - Legislation. H.R. 2344 (Box 69)
    - Legislation. H.R. 2685. Regulations (Box 69)
    - Legislation. H.R. 4644. (Box 69)
    - Legislation. H.R. 9245. Postal Pay Reclassification (Box 69)
    - Legislation. H.R. 11380 (Box 69)
    - Legislation. Public Law. 669 (Box 69)
    - Parcel Post Weights. (Public Law 199) (Box 70)
    - Postal Pay Raises. Info. 1954 (Box 70)
  - Post Office and Civil Service
    - Copies of Bills.1956 (Box 70)
    - Copies of Bills. 1957-1958 (Box 70)
    - Federal Employees Pay Raise Legislation (Box 70)
    - H.R. 8894. Retirement Annuity (Box 70)
    - Legislation. 1955-1956 (Box 70)
    - Legislation. 1957-1958 (Box 70)
  - Post Office Department. 1955 (Box 71)
  - Press. Statements to (Box 71)
  - Public Health Legislation. H.R. 9397. H.R. 8149 (Box 71)
  - Public Lands:
    - General Legislation. 1953-1954 (Box 71)
    - General Legislation. 1955-1956 (Box 71)
    - Legislation.1957 (Box 71)
    - Legislation. Land withdrawals for military purposes. H.R. 627 (Box 71)
    - Legislation. H.R. 4023 (Box 72)
    - Legislation. H.R. 4023 (Box 72)
    - Legislation. H.R. 4646 Ellsworth Bill (Box 72)
  - Public Lands Subcommittee. General (Box 72)
  - Public Works:
    - Copies of Bills.1956 (Box 72)
    - Copies of Bills. 1957-1958 (Box 72)
    - Legislation. 1955-1956 (Box 72)
    - Legislation. 1957-1958 (Box 72)
  - Publications. Misc. (Box 73)
  - Queen, J. Richard (Box 73)
  - Queen. For Dick (Box 73)
  - Questionnaire (Box 73)
  - Railroad Legislation (Box 73)
  - Railroad Retirement Act. H.R. 356 (Box 73)
  - Railroad Retirement Board. 1955 (Box 73)
  - Reconstruction Finance Corporation. 1955 (Box 73)
  - Refugee Relief Act. H.R. 6481 (Box 73)
  - Refugees. Hungarian (Box 73)
  - Refugee Relief Program (Box 73)
  - Rent Controls. H.R. 4507 (Box 74)
  - Requests:
    - 1954 (Box 74)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 74)
    - 1957 (Box 74)
    - 1957 (Box 75)
  - Resolutions.1954 (Box 75)
  - Resolutions. 1955-1956 (Box 75)
  - Resolutions.1958 (Box 75)
  - Rollman. Mr. H.W. Re: World Construction Plan (Box 75)
  - St. Lawrence Seaway (Box 75)
  - Mr. Shuford. Biographical Sketch (Box 75)
  - Judge Shuford's Voting Record (Box 75)
  - Small Business: (Box 76)
    - Administration.1955 (Box 76)
    - Committee. Bills. 1957-1958 (Box 76)
    - Committee. Legislation. 1957-1958 (Box 76)
    - H.R. 4665. To Amend the Small Business Act of1953to make Small Business Adm. a permanent agency of the government, etc. (Box 76)
    - Small Business (Box 76)
  - Smith, Willis (Box 76)
  - Social Security:
    - H.R. 9709. Unemployment Compensation Program and Proposed Amendments (Box 76)
    - Social Security (Box 76)
  - Stamp Account (Box 76)
  - Stationery Account:
    - 1953-1954 (Box 76)
    - 1955 (Box 76)
    - 1956 (Box 76)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 76)
  - Department of State. 1955 (Box 76)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board (Box 77)
  - Proposed Tariff Changes (Box 77)
  - Taxation:
    - Co-ops. H.R. 1559 (Box 77)
    - Co-ops (Box 77)
    - Excess Profits Tax (Box 77)
    - Federal Excise Tax (Box 77)
    - H.R. 3078. Jenkins (Box 77)